<Document>
  # AULIN MK.II SPACE-TO-GROUND SALVAGE VESSEL
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OreProcessor"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponTurretL85Autocannon"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ResearchAndDevelopmentServer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MachineArtifactAnalyzer"/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Large

  [color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 1-3

  [color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Antimatter Engine (AME)

  [color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] All

  [color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  [color=#a4885c]Armaments:[/color] L85 90mm Autocannon x2, L-1 Phalanx x2

  "The Aulin Mk.II vessel is a space-to-ground transport shuttle made by Foxton DeLacewing shipyards, capable of doing expeditions, having a sizable salvage bay, and having an artifact research chamber. Made to compete with the SKR Meteor with it's own Heavy Bluespace Engine."

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  ## 1. Power supply

  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESAdvanced"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationWallBasic"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the Antimatter Engine (AME) generator is functional (View below.)
  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is charging.
  - Check that the Engineering APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check that the Server Room APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check that the Bridge APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.

  ## 1.2. Antimatter Engine (AME) reactor unit.
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeController"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeJar"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the AME control device is anchored to the floor and connected to a 3x3 containment shielding structure.
  - Check that the AME control device is connected to the cable terminal of your SMES via HV.
  - Check the fuel remaining of the generator unit.
  - Enable Injection.
  (Note: AMEs automatically generate power equivalent to demand.)

  ## 2. Atmospherics

  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirCanister"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that both air canisters are anchored to their respective connector ports.
  - Check that outgoing distribution air pump is ON.

  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>

  - Enable external waste loop pump. (Located behind AME.)

  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.

  ## Sidenotes

  * - Aulin vessels come with a CTLA-160 Heavy Bluespace Core rated for a max jump distance of ~25km.


  * - Due to lack of plating, the AME is not well protected. Making direct hits to the back of the vessel extremely devastating.


  * - Aulin vessels are equipped with a power monitoring computer that can be used to appraise the ship's total power production and consumption. An unmodified Aulin vessel requires ~60 kW of power to remain operational.

  * - Due to the lack of power from the ship's retrothrusters, pilots are required to be adept at switching flight modes to prevent accidental collision
</Document>
